Haley Trumbo

Aloha! I'm an enthusiastic and dedicated worker with 8 years of knowledge in many sides of the restaurant industry. I am communicative, team-oriented, and optimistic with ample experience in customer service, menu knowledge, and working in a fast-paced environment.

EXPERIENCE

Waikiki Brewing Company, Waikiki, HI — Server

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021

<u>Server</u> - Served sections between 5-12 tables in a casual setting. Expected to have accurate knowledge on the brewing process and proper descriptive language to assist guests in choosing their beer. Expected to stay on top of proper COVID regulations for myself and for each guest.

Primavera Ristorante, San Ramon, CA — Server, Assistant Manager, Event Planner, Host

Aug 2014 - Aug 2020

<u>Server</u> - Thrived in a team setting within a high volume, fine dining restaurant. Served sections between 8-12 tables and banquet parties up to 50 guests. Expected to have knowledge of wine pairings, and extensive knowledge of all food and drink menu items.

<u>Assistant Manager</u> - Managed daily operations and guest complaints to ensure guest satisfaction. Managed restaurant workload and worked as a communicative and energetic support to staff.

<u>Event Planner</u> - Booked banquet parties for up to 100 people. Worked with party hosts to provide for their party's specifications, expected to respond to inquiries and party hosts in a timely manner to ensure quality planning.

821 Puunani Pl. Honolulu, Hl 96817

(925) 413-9839

trumbo.haley@gmail.com

SKILLS

Cicerone Certified Beer Server

Exceptional customer service

Efficient in multiple POS systems

Stress-tolerance

Food safety

Effective communication

EDUCATION

Diablo Valley College, San Ramon, CA 2014-2019 Associates Degree Allied Health

University of Nevada - Las Vegas

2017-2018

Pre-Nursing

Health Care Training & Career Consultants, Honolulu, HI

2020

CNA Training

REFERENCES

Manuel Ybarra (925)-207-1440 GM at Primavera Ristorante

Matthew Harwell (702) 473-9523 GM at Carson Kitchen

Rob Peterson (925) 389-6595 GM at Rock House

Carson Kitchen, Las Vegas, NV — Server

Jan 2018 - Aug 2018

<u>Server</u> - Served sections between 8-12 tables and banquet parties up to 30 guests in a casual setting in the heart of downtown Las Vegas. Expected to have extensive knowledge on a changing seasonal menu with fine dining ingredients and craft cocktails.

Rock House Pub & Grill, Livermore, CA — Server

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

<u>Server</u> - Served sections between 10-20 tables in a fast-paced, high volume, sports pub setting. Expected to be well versed and up to date in a rotating 20 beer tap with majority local craft brews.